jumpbook.in 2014-06-23

# privacy_policy » Jumpbook - Jump in Your Dream Book

**Privacy Policy**

We are running this multifunctional social network website and we shall have certain personal sensitive information in our custody which is provided by the visitor while using different functions of this site, hence as per Rule 4 of the Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information)Rules, 2011, we are required to publish this privacy policy on this website. 

Being a responsible service provider, we respect the privacy of each individual who visits this website. Accordingly, we would like to inform you regarding the way we would use your personal sensitive Information. We recommend you to read this privacy policy so that you   
understand our approach towards the use of your personal data. 

Anyone browsing through this website or providing any information/personal data is deemed to be in agreement with the following privacy policy: 

**Coverage of privacy policy**

This privacy policy is to inform you of the safety and use of your personal information which is collected during your visit to this website. 

This privacy policy applies to the majority of our websites, however there may be occasions where there is a need to have a slightly different privacy policy. Whenever a website of Jumpbook has a different privacy policy it will be made clear that the privacy policy differs from this general Jumpbook privacy policy. On your journey around the Jumpbook websites please check the privacy policy of each website which you visit and do not assume that this privacy policy applies to all Jumpbook websites. 

**Responsibility of the personal information collected on this site**

Your personal data is controlled ultimately by 

_Jumpbook Tech Pvt. Ltd_

., a company registered under Companies Act, 1956 bearing Identification number B85298735 having its registered office is at B-1,Street no-5,Dwarka mod,Uttam Nagar,New Delhi-110059. 

**Alert for children**

Our website is exclusively for use by persons above the age of 13 years. We do not wish to collect, use, provide or process in any other form, any personal information of children under the age of 13. We, therefore, also ask you, if you are under 13 years old, please do not send us your personal information (for example, your name, address and email address). 

If you are under 13 years old and you nevertheless wish to ask a question or use this website in anyway which requires you to submit your personal information please get your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf. 

**Objective behind collection of your data**

One of the purposes of our website is to inform you of who we are and what we do. We collect and use personal information (including name, address, telephone number and email) to better provide you with the required services, or information. We would therefore use your personal information in order to: 

• respond to queries or requests submitted by you 

• process orders or applications submitted by you 

• administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you 

have with us 

• anticipate and resolve problems with any goods or services supplied to you 

• create products or services that may meet your needs. 

To optimise our services we may wish to use your personal data for direct marketing. As we respect your privacy we will only use your personal data for this purpose when you are aware thereof and if required we will request your consent prior to using your personal data for direct marketing. 

Additionally, if at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the above purposes, please contact us as set out below. We will stop the use of your information for such purposes as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so. 

In addition, the collected personal data will (occasionally) be transferred to selected third parties, which may be located outside India as part of the services offered to you through our site. By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside India or one of our service providers is located outside Indian Territory. 

These third parties will not use your personal information for any other purposes than what we have agreed with them. Jumpbook requests those third parties to implement adequate levels of protection in order to safeguard your personal information. 

We respect your personal information and therefore, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected if we transfer your information outside India in this way. In addition, if you use our services while you are outside India, your information may be transferred into that particular country in order to provide you with those services. 

Except as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless we are legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime) or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers or other individuals. 

Please be assured that we will not use your information for any of the purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to use your information in this way when submitting the information or at a later stage. 

**Collection of non-personal information**

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the website from which you linked to our website. We may also aggregate details which you have submitted to the site (for example, your age and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this web site. We may from time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in connection with this website. 

**Our interaction**

We are interested in your views, and we value feedback from our clients and visitors, we therefore have set up notice boards, newsgroups, feedback, email, forum facilities and/ or chat rooms. If at any time this website offers any chat rooms, notice board facilities, newsgroups etc we may collect the personal information that you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy. 

However, we can of course not control and be responsible for other parties' use of the personal information which you make available to them through this website. We encourage you to be careful about what personal information you disclose in this way. 

**Accuracy of records**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review, change or delete the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below. 

**Safety of your personal data**

As we value your personal information, we will ensure an adequate level of protection. We have therefore implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and will update these measures as new   
technology becomes available, as appropriate. 

**Use of your personal information submitted to other web sites**

On our websites, we may have links to other websites or you are referred to our website through a link from another website. As you can imagine, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites. Such content is subject to their terms of use and any additional guidelines and privacy information provided in relation to that use on their website. 

We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit to better understand your rights and obligations especially when you are submitting any type of content on those third party website. Please contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions. 

**Changes to this policy**

From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any substantial changes to this privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal data we will post these changes on this page and will do our best to notify you of any significant changes.   
Please check our privacy policy on a regular basis. 

**How you can contact us**

If you would like to contact jumpbook about our privacy policy, please visit our contact us page.
